You need a table that you can kind of clear away and kind of have you work right in front of you.
What I've got here is--it's about the right size, maybe a little bit small because I have a bunch of things on it right now.
I might not normally have everything that I use for circuit bending on the table at one time and I've just kind of done that here because we're making these videos, but you do want a space that kind of a nice space you can clear and put your project in front of you, a place where your soldering iron is handy.
If you're right handed you put it over here, if you're left handed you put it over there, kind of obvious.
Whatever the material that the workbench is made out of is kind of important.
This one's made out of wood which means I want to be kind of maybe extra careful about where my soldering iron is and make sure it's in the stand, right?
Or in the standalone stand so that I don't burn my workbench.
And the same is true for other materials, one thing that you can get for a highly combustible surfaces like a wooden surface is.
If you want to, you can get a heat resistant work surface at like--I guess you can go to a hardware store or lumberyard and get like a concrete fiber board, something like that, or you could go to a--lot of craft stores will sell like a metal heat-resistant work surface that's used for like working with lamp work, with glass and that kind of thing.
So yeah, workbench that's about the right size, you can have your soldering iron there, you want to be near an electrical outlet where you can put the soldering iron and have enough space to work.